

ANDY CHEN

North Jakarta, Indonesian • andychen9979@gmail.com • (+62) 812-6700-6823 andychen00.github.io • linkedin.com/in/andy-chen-78504620b

#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Andy Chen is a developer with 3 year of experience. He serves as a junior developer in his company now. Beside that, he also have a lot of knowledge in software development such us programming skill, system development, UI/UX design and many else. he also already done several of project about web and mobile application.

## **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

**Evotech Distribusi Co.** (IT solution prodiver)

Puri Kembangan, West Jakarta Feb 2022 – Feb 2023

Mobile and Web Developer Intern

- Built, develop and maintain web/mobile application for warehouse project based using Outsystems
- Perform bug fixing or debugging for developed application that can help to optimize and maintain the app well
- Collaborating with UI/UX designer to ensure the design were efficient and tecnically sound
- Assist in gathering user requirement, design UI application and user acceptance testing
- Ensuring proper documentation and report of all programs

Ifabula Digital Kreasi Co. (IT solution prodiver)

Green Lake City, Tangerang

Feb 2023 - Now

- Junior Developer (Outsystem Developer)
- Improve my skill and knowledge of using Outsystems
- Working with a team project and comunation with client to discuss user requirement for project
- Have experience in managing, collaborating and communicating well in a team
- Integrating with REST API in several project
- Working with SSMS databases and performing queries

# **EDUCATION**

**Binus University** 

Kemanggisan, West Jakarta August 2019 - 2023

Bachelor of Computer

Major in Computer Science - Mobile Application and Technology

GPA: 3.75/4.0:

Relevant Coursework: Web Development; Application Development; UI/UX Analysis; Database System, Operating System; Algorithms;

#### **PROJECTS HANDLE**

#### **Challengers App (Thesis Project)**

- Help with designing interface using java with android studio tools
- Perform database design to help application store data using Outsystems
- Exposed API and logic to make sure the application can do CRUD action to database
- Ensure the security of the program like perform hashing, encrypt and individual access key

### Gudang2Go (Warehouse Web and Mobile Application)

- Designed, developed, and maintained web/mobile applications for warehouse projects
- Debugged and resolved application issues to ensure smooth functionality
- Worked alongside UI/UX designers to create efficient design and user friendly application
- Participated in gathering user needs, designing user interfaces, and performing user acceptance tests
- Produced comprehensive documentation and detailed reports for all program in application

### IRIS Monitoring (Website for monitoring internal working process)

- Built, develop and maintain web application for IRIS Monitoring Project
- Collaborated on team projects while communicating with clients to determine user requirements
- Gained experience in teamwork, including managing, cooperating, and fostering strong communication within teams
- Create report and documentation for all program in the application

# BOA/ Back Office Aggregator (Website for manage bank transaction for internal used)

- Improve the BOA project that already exist and develop new feature for the application
- Collaborated on team projects to discuss about the improvement of the application
- Gained experience in teamwork, including managing and cooperating with different team
- Incorporated REST APIs into projects to ensure seamless integration.
- Utilized SSMS databases to perform advanced queries and data management.

## ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Technical: Java, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Outsystems, Relational Database, RESTful API
- Tools: Android Studio, Outsystems, VSCode, SSMS
- Languages: English, Mandarin, Indonesian
- Certifictions & Training: HMS foundation course, OS Developer